A Guide to the Governor Gerald L. Baliles Executive Papers, 1986-1990
Library of Virginia
- Series I: 1986 (accession 33702)
  - Sub-Series E: Cabinet
    - Teenage Pregnancy (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Virginia School for Deaf and Blind (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - E.3 - Secretary of Education - State Agencies
    - Department of Education (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Department of Education - Lancaster County (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Department of Education - School Attendance for 4 year olds (Commission on Excellence in Education) (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - The Science Museum of Virginia (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - State Education Assistance Authority (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Commission for the Arts (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Educational Loan Authority (VELA) (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Virginia State Library (part one of two) (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Virginia State Library (part two of two) (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - E.4 - Secretary of Finance
    - Correspondence sent and/or copied to Governor's Office, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Memorandums sent or copied to Governor's Office, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - E.4 - Secretary of Finance - State Agencies
    - Department of Accounts - Comptroller (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Department of Accounts - Prompt Payment Act (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Department of Planning and Budget (part one of two) (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Department of Planning and Budget (part two of two) (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Department of Taxation (part one of two) (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Department of Taxation (part two of two) (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Department of the Treasury (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Department of the Treasury - Division of Unclaimed Property (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - E.5 - Secretary of Human Resources
    - Correspondence send and/or copied to Governor's Office, 1986 December 24-November 6 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence send and/or copied to Governor's Office, 1986 October 20-September 2 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence send and/or copied to Governor's Office, 1986 August 29-July 18 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence send and/or copied to Governor's Office, 1986 July 17-May 27 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence send and/or copied to Governor's Office, 1986 May 23-April 11 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence send and/or copied to Governor's Office, 1986 April 10-January 10 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Memorandums sent or copied to Governor's Office, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Deputy Secretary of Human Resources, Correspondence send and/or copied to Governor's Office, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - E.5 - Secretary of Human Resources - State Agencies
    - Department for the Aging (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Department of Health (part one of two) (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Department of Health (part two of two) (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Department of Health - Certificate of Public Need (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Department of Health Regulatory Boards (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Department of Medical Assistance Services (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Department of Mental Health and Mental Retardation (part one of two) (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Department of Mental Health and Mental Retardation (part two of two) (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Department of Rehabilitative Services (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Department of Social Services (part one of four) (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Department of Social Services (part two of four) (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Department of Social Services (part three of four) (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Department of Social Services (part four of four) (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Department of Social Services - Division of Child Support Enforcement (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Department of Volunteerism (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Governor's Employment and Training Department (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Rights of the Disabled (Board and Department) (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Health Services Cost Review Council (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - E.5 - Secretary of Human Resources - Human Resources Topics
    - Child Abuse (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Magnetic Resonance Imaging Service (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - E.6 - Secretary of Natural Resources
    - Correspondence sent and or copied to Governor's Office, 1986 December 31-October 14 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence sent and/or copied to Governor's Office, 1986 October 10-January 29 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Deputy Secretary of Natural Resources, Correspondence and Memorandums sent and/or copied to Governor's Office, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - E.6 - Secretary of Natural Resources - Boards and Commissions
    - Appalachian Regional Commission (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Delmarva Advisory Council and Rural Ministries (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Ohio River Valley Water Sanitation Commission (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Virginia Hazardous Waste Facility Siting Council (HWFSC) (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - E.6 - Secretary of Natural Resources - State Agencies
    - Commission of Game and Inland Fisheries (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Council on the Environment (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Department of Conservation and Historic Resources (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Department of Emergency Services - Drought, 1986 December 1-September 12 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Department of Emergency Services - Drought, 1986 August 27-August 1 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Department of Emergency Services - Drought, 1986 July 31-July 21 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Department of Emergency Services - Drought, 1986 July 18-1985 December 30 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Department of Mines, Minerals and Energy (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Department of Waste Management (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Marine Resources Commission (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - State Air Pollution Control Board (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - State Water Control Board (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Resources Authority (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - E.6 - Secretary of Natural Resources - Natural Resources Topices
    - Cedar Island (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - False Cape State Park (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Public Beaches (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - E.7 - Secretary of Transportation and Public Safety
    - Correspondence sent and/or copied to Governor's Office, 1986 December 30-November 14 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence sent and/or copied to Governor's Office, 1986 November 7-September 22 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence sent and/or copied to Governor's Office, 1986 September 19-July 30 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence sent and/or copied to Governor's Office, 1986 July 25-July 1 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence sent and/or copied to Governor's Office, 1986 June 30-May 23 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence sent and/or copied to Governor's Office, 1986 May 20-March 25 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence sent and/or copied to Governor's Office, 1986 March 24-January 21 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Memorandums sent or copied to Governor's Office, 1986 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Deputy Secretary of Transportation, Correspondence and Memorandums sent and/or copied to Governor's Office, 1986 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Deputy Secretary of Public Safety, Correspondence and Memorandums sent and/or copied to Governor's Office, 1986 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - E.7 - Secretary of Transportation and Public Safety - State Agencies
    - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Department of Aviation (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Department of Corrections (part one) (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Department of Corrections (part two) (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Department of Correctional Education (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Department of Criminal Justice Services (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Department of Emergency Services (Box 35, Folder 5a)
    - Department of Highways and Transportation (part one) (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Department of Highways and Transportation (part two) (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Department of Highways and Transportation (part three) (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Department of Highways and Transportation (part four) (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Department of Highways and Transportation (part five) (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Department of Highways and Transportation (part six) (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Department of Highways and Transportation (part seven) (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Department of Highways and Transportation (part eight) (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Department of Highways and Transportation - Route 28 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Department of Highways and Transportation - Route 29 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Department of Highways and Transportation - Route 58 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Department of Highways and Transportation - Route 288 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Department of Highways and Transportation - Outer Beltway (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Department of Highways and Transportation - Providence and Courthouse Roads (Chesterfield County) (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Department of Military Affairs (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Department of Motor Vehicles (part one) (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Department of Motor Vehicles (part two) (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Department of State Police (part one) (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Department of State Police (part two) (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Port Authority (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - E.7 - Secretary of Transportation and Public Safety - Transportation Topics
    - Airport Transfer Act (part one) (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Airport Transfer Act (part two) (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Transportation-General Needs and Funding (part one) (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Transportation-General Needs and Funding (part two) (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series F: General Assembly
    - Special Session, 1986 September 15 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - House Joint Resolution 155 Report (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - General Correspondence (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Block Grant Notices to Members (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Senate and House, Members' Lists (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Senate Correspondence, A-D (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Senate Correspondence, E-J (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Senate Correspondence, M-W (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - House of Delegates Correspondence, A-E (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - House of Delegates Correspondence, F-M (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - House of Delegates Correspondence, P-W (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series G: Secretary of the Commonwealth
    - Gubernatorial Appointments (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series H: Legislative
    - Auditor of Public Accounts (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Commission on Veteran's Affairs (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Department of Workman's Compensation - Industrial Commission of Virginia (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Division of Legislative Services (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Division of Legislative Automated Services (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Code Commission (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series I: Attorney General
    - Attorney General's Office - Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Department of Law - Division of Veteran's Claims (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series J: Judicial
    - General (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Judicial Inquiry and Review Commission (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Virginia State Bar (empty) (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Supreme Court (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series K: State Corporation Commission
    - General (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Bureau of Financial Institutions (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Bureau of Insurance (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series L: Lt. Governor
    - L. Douglas Wilder (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series M: Virginia Liaison Office
    - Correspondence and Memorandums, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series N: United States Government
    - Senate - General (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Senate - John W. Warner (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Senate - Paul S. Trible (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Virginia Congressional Delegation (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Virginia Congressmen, Bateman through Wolf (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - House of Representatives - General (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - H.R. 5021 - Interstate Mail Order (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Department of Agriculture (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Department of the Air Force (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Department of the Army (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Department of the Army - Corps of Engineers (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Department of Commerce (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Department of Education (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Department of Energy (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Department of Health and Human Services (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Department of Housing and Urban Development (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Department of Immigration and Naturalization Service (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Department of the Interior (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Department of Justice (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Department of Labor (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Department of the Navy and United States Marine Corps (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Department of the Navy, EMPRESS II (Electromagnetic Pulse Radiation Environment Simulator for Ships), 1984-1986 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Department of State (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Department of Transportation (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Department of Transportation, Coast Guard (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Department of Transportation, CONRAIL (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Federal Emergency Management Agency (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Federal Highway Administration (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - General (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - General Services Administration (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Gramm-Rudman-Hollings Bill (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Highway Trust Fund (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - National Transportation Safety Board (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Office of the Attorney General (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Office of Technology Assessment (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Postal Service (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - The U.S. Savings Bond Campaign (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Small Business Administration (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Social Security Administration (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Supreme Court (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Veteran's Administration (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - The White House (Box 44, Folder 16)
- Series II. 1987 (accession 33702)
  Notable records include a letter to Governor Baliles from Mark R. Warner, head of MRW Enterprises, dated 21 July 1987, requesting an introductory meeting with the Governor and expressing his interest to get involved in Virginia politics (Associations, National Governors' Association, Box 50, Folder 3); several memorandums on Executive Mansion renovations and the Executive Mansion Anniversary Project (Governor's Office, Executive Mansion, Box 55, Folder 4); Virginia Military Advisory Commission, First Report of the Legal Affairs Committee, submitted by Attorney General Mary Sue Terry, 1 September 1987 (Governor's Office, Virginia Military Advisory Commission, Box 64, Folder 1); minutes (5 June 1987, 17 July 1987, 11 September 1987, 2 October 1987 and 16 October 1987) of the Joint Subcommittee Studying the Adoption of New Lyrics for the Official Song of the Commonwealth (Legislative, Division of Legislative Services, Box 87, Folder 7); minutes of meeting at the Executive Mansion with Virginia Congressional Delegation, 19 January 1987, attached to 6 February 1987 letter to Governor Baliles from Senator John W. Warner (United States Government, Box 89, Folder 2).
  - Sub-Series A: General Correspondence
    - Acid Rain (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - AIDS (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Capital Punishment, Sample Letters (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Chesapeake Bay Bridge Tunnel Commission (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Chesapeake Bay Draft Agreement (part one) (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Chesapeake Bay Draft Agreement (part two) (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Chesapeake Bay Draft Agreement (part three) (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Chesapeake Bay Draft Agreement (part four) (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Chesapeake Bay Draft Agreement (part five) (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Child Care (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Drug and Alcohol Abuse (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Drunk Driving (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Education (part one) (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Education (part two) (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Employment (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Flag Requests (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - General (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - High Occupancy Vehicles (HOV) (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Horse Center (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Housing - General (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Infant Mortality (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Lottery (part one) (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Lottery (part two) (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - News Clippings - General (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Parental Consent (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Patrick Henry Memorial Foundation (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Poplar Forest (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Retirement Bill 55/30 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - School Children's Letters and Requests - Samples (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Scouts - Boy/Eagle/Girl (part one) (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Scouts - Boy/Eagle/Girl (part two) (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Scouts - Boy/Eagle/Girl (part three) (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Seat Belts (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Smoking - General (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Speed Limit (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Tax Amnesty (Windfall) (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Taxes - General (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Trade - General (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Unanswered - Samples (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - United Nations (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - United Way (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Veterans and Veterans Cemetery (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Water - General (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series B: Associations
    - General (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - National Governors' Association - Vice-Chair and Chair-Elect (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - National Governors' Association - Correspondence (part one) (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - National Governors' Association - Correspondence (part two) (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - [See Series VI. Miscellaneous for additional National Governors' Association Records.]
    - Southern Governors' Association - Correspondence (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Southern Governors' Association - International Education (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Southern States Energy Board (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series C: Localities
    - Cities - General (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Counties - General (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Towns - General (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series D: Governor's Office
    - Bicentennial of U.S. Constitution (part one) (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Bicentennial of U.S. Constitution (part two) (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Block Grants (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Budget (part one) (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Budget (part two) (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Budget (part three) (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Budget (part four) (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Budget (part five) (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Certificates of Recognition - See Messages from the Governor
    - Commission on Efficiency in Government (part one) (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Commission on Efficiency in Government (part two) (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Commission on Efficiency in Government (part three) (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Community Action Agencies (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Congratulations - Birthday (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Congratulations - General (part one) (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Congratulations - General (part two) (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Congratulations - General (part three) (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Congratulations - Wedding (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Constituent Correspondence - See Also Staff Correspondence
    - Constituent Correspondence, H. Benson Dendy, III, Special Assistant, 1987 December 30-December 8 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Constituent Correspondence, H. Benson Dendy, III, Special Assistant, 1987 December 7-November 18 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Constituent Correspondence, H. Benson Dendy, III, Special Assistant, 1987 November 17-October 16 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Constituent Correspondence, H. Benson Dendy, III, Special Assistant, 1987 October 15-September 22 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Constituent Correspondence, H. Benson Dendy, III, Special Assistant, 1987 September 21-August 28 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Constituent Correspondence, H. Benson Dendy, III, Special Assistant, 1987 August 27-July 31 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Constituent Correspondence, H. Benson Dendy, III, Special Assistant, 1987 July 29-July 10 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Constituent Correspondence, H. Benson Dendy, III, Special Assistant, 1987 July 9-June 4 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Constituent Correspondence, H. Benson Dendy, III, Special Assistant, 1987 June 3-May 8 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Constituent Correspondence, H. Benson Dendy, III, Special Assistant, 1987 May 7-April 17 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Constituent Correspondence, H. Benson Dendy, III, Special Assistant, 1987 April 16-March 12 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Constituent Correspondence, H. Benson Dendy, III, Special Assistant, 1987 March 11-February 18 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Constituent Correspondence, H. Benson Dendy, III, Special Assistant, 1987 February 17-January 19 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Excellence in Education (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Executive Mansion (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Get Well Letters (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - [Governor's] Fellows Program (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Governor's General Correspondence, 1987 December 29-December 8 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Governor's General Correspondence, 1987 December 7-November 18 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Governor's General Correspondence, 1987 November 16-October 30 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Governor's General Correspondence, 1987 October 29-September 22 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Governor's General Correspondence, 1987 September 21-August 13 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Governor's General Correspondence, 1987 August 11-July 6 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Governor's General Correspondence, 1987 July 3-June 2 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Governor's General Correspondence, 1987 June 1-May 6 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Governor's General Correspondence, 1987 May 5-April 21 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Governor's General Correspondence, 1987 April 10-March 27 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Governor's General Correspondence, 1987 March 25-February 15 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Governor's General Correspondence, 1987 February 13-January 5 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Governors Other States - See Other States, Governor
    - Granville Meade Scholarship Fund (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Greetings from the Governor (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Intern Program (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - International Education (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - International Trade Commission (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Jewish Community Issues (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Liability Insurance (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Literacy (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Mail Trends (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Main Street Program (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Meetings and Conventions, 1989-1992 and 1994 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Messages from the Governor, 1987 January-April (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Messages from the Governor, 1987 May-August (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Messages from the Governor, 1987 September-December (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - [Messages from the Governor] - Certificates of Recognition, A-D (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - [Messages from the Governor] - Certificates of Recognition, E-I (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - [Messages from the Governor] - Certificates of Recognition, J-N (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - [Messages from the Governor] - Certificates of Recognition, O-U (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - [Messages from the Governor] - Certificates of Recognition, V-Y (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - [Messages from the Governor] - Proclamations (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - [Messages from the Governor] - See Also State of the Commonwealth Address
    - Metro Washington Airports Authority (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Model General Assembly-YMCA (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - National Geography Awareness Week (part one) (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - National Geography Awareness Week (part two) (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - News Clippings (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Other States - General (part one) (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Other States - General (part two) (Box 60, Folder 3)